Finding aid to the Mary Daly papers SSC.MS.00637
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. Writings, 1973-2004; 30.376 linear feet (38 containers)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 - Sublime: Divine Attributes (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 - Sublime: Trinity (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 - Sublime: Words (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Doctrine of Incarnation (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Mediation (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Plastics (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation:Plastic Feminism, Copenhagen (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Sacrifice and Suffering (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Charity and Therapy and Friendship (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Conversion (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Doublethink (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Language (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Mediated Knowledge (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Plastic Environment (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Plastic Feminism (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Mediation (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Nuclear Missions (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Nuclear Missions - Phoenix (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Missions, Missionaries (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Sacramento, Eucharist, Mass (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Sacraments, Penance (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Plastic Passions (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Pseudo-atmospheres (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Plastic Religion (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Nuclear Missions - Trident (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Sacraments (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 - Sublimation: Witch Craze and Rise of Protestantism (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Prologue: The Second Sphere - The Race Elementals (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste: Alchemy (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Animals (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Elements - air (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Elements - fire (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Elements - perversion (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Elements - water (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Memory (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Memory II and Canada Conference (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Passions, Female Fear (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Masochistic Passions - anger (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Masochistic Passions - fear, daring (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Masochistic Passions - hate, aversion, sorrow, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Masochistic Passions - love, desire, joy, hope, despair (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Skin (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste: Therapy (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 - Touchable Caste/Race: Tracking of Women and Nature (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Bonding (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Dragons (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Elements (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Fury (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Gnome Group Words (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Legitimization and Breaking Out, Mother Seton, etc. (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Memory (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Lusty Passions - fear, daring (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Lusty Passions - hate, aversion, sorrow, rage (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Lusty Passions - love, desire, joy, hope, despair (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Prudence (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Virtues, Volcanic Temperance (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 - Breaking Out: Volcanoes (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons, Labels, Naming: General Notes (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Athenas (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons, Labels, Naming: Labels (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Naming (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons, Labels, Naming: Pseudo-feminism (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Athenic Passions - Anger (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Athenic Passions - love, desire, joy, hope, despair (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Athenic Passions - hate, aversion, sorrow (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy: Therapy (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy: Waves (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Prologue to the Third Sphere (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Angels (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Auras, Atmospheres (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Diversity (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Rhythm (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Soul (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Spheres (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 - Auras, Atmospheres, Angels: Stars (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 9 - Wanderlust: Final Cause (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 10 - Wonderlust (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 10 - Wonderlust: Muses (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Epilogue - Dracula's Defeat (Box 19)
  - Copies from Mongraphs (Box 19)
  - Articles loose in box, 1982 (Box 19)
  - 'Dear Diary' document loose in box (Box 19)
  - Beyond God the Father Chapter 6 - Second Proof (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Outline (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Introduction (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust The First Realm (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust The Second Realm (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 4 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust The Third Realm (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 10 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 11 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 12 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Non-Chapter 13 (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 - Tides, Tidy, Demons: Athenic Passions - fear, daring (Box 19)
  - Newspapers (originally in Beacon R.R. folder), 1978 (Box 20)
  - Beacon - public relations, 1977-1980 (Box 20)
  - Andrea Dworkin, 2000 (Box 20)
  - Arts, Etc. newspaper, 1996-1997 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and notes, 2007 (Box 20)
  - Beacon Press, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Beacon Press - contract, 1972-1988 (Box 20)
  - Beacon contract for Pure Lust - sent to Charlotte, 1982-1991 (Box 20)
  - Beacon contract for Wickedary, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Beacon contract for The Church and the Second Sex, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Beacon contract for Pure Lust, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Outercourse contract, 1992 (Box 20)
  - Beacon Press Pure Lust foreign rights, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Quintessence contract history - Jill Kneerim and Helene Atwan, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Harper: Wickedary contract, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Church and the Second Sex - Harper: Royalties and Sales, 1976-1986 (Box 20)
  - Harper and Row, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Harper and Row - California, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Wickedary promotion (Box 20)
  - Boston Globe article, 1997 (Box 20)
  - "Science, Order, and Creativity" from 3-ring binder (Box 20)
  - A. E. 's Dialogue Group on David Bohm (Box 20)
  - Michel Dion, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Clippings for Canny Comments (Box 20)
  - Newspaper clippings - miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1993-1997 (Box 20)
  - "C. C. Watch" newsletter, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Periodicals, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - billboards into outer space, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - radiation, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - Expanding Foreground here - computers, invasion of privacy, con-fusion, rain forest, virtual reality, genetic manipulation, incest, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - Expanding Foreground here - Genocide, woman battering, radiation, destruction of animals/hunting, Bobbit, destruction of environment, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - Expanding Foreground here - attacks on feminism, rape, toxic waste: spread, overpopulation, Mormons, millennialism, assimilation, death/life after Kubler-Ross, general, 1993-1995 (Box 20)
  - Clippings - Expanding Foreground here - Into Minds: strategies, erasure (Box 20)
  - Abortion, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Clippings of Films, 1993 (Box 20)
  - New Age (Box 20)
  - Dismemberment of Goddesses by Women, foregrounding of here (Box 20)
  - Outercourse book jacket (Box 20)
  - Pure Lust book jacket design (Box 20)
  - Quintessence poster (Box 20)
  - Amazon Grace footnotes introduction (Box 20)
  - Amazon Grace - global warming articles, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Articles (most likely related to Amazon Grace) (Box 20)
  - Magazine article (most likely a resource for Amazon Grace), 2000 (Box 20)
  - Periodicals, 2002-2003 (Box 21)
  - Beyond God the Father research, 1971-1972 (Box 21)
  - Beyond God the Father draft (Box 21)
  - Beyond God the Father manuscript (Box 21)
  - Quintessence manuscript draft (Box 21)
  - Outercourse Spinifex Press, 2001-2003 (Box 21)
  - Women's Press - Adele Munchin, Fith Liddell, Anthology by Charlotte Cole, Kathy Gale, 1999-2001 (Box 21)
  - Women's Press - Quintessence contracts, royalties, 1996-1999 (Box 21)
  - Women's Press - U.S. distribution, 1997-1999 (Box 21)
  - The Women's Press - Quintessence contract, 1999 (Box 21)
  - Quintessence cover (Box 21)
  - Beacon Press, 2001 (Box 21)
  - Social Security, 1999-2002 (Box 21)
  - Celebrations (Box 21)
  - Wickedary notes (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 21)
  - C. Glamour (Box 21)
  - E. Guides (Box 21)
  - New Bedford rape (Box 21)
  - Wickedary - Its History/Metamystery of Man (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Core I xeroxes of cards, clippings, early drafts, footnotes (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Core II clippings, obsolete, originals (Box 21)
  - Wickedary notes on core divisions (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix I, part 2 - Dummy Class Look and Sound the same as Elemental Words (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix I, part 3, Elementaries of Third Class, without background (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix I, part 4 - Dummy Elementary Terms and Phrases, Reversals and Doublehand (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix I, part 5 - Pseudofeminist Dummies (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix I - Reversal (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix II - Be-Laughing (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix III - Sense of Direction (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Appendix IV - Thirteen (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Intro Material - Pronunciation (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Proposal - Introductory Material, E Guides to the Wickedary (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Proposal - Introductory Material and Spelling (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Proposal - Introductory Material - A: The Wickedary: Its History, Mystery (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Proposal - core words, be-word, eyes and wise, whys word, weird words, sin words, mean words (Box 21)
  - Wickedary Introductory Elemental Glamour of Grammar (Box 21)
  - Introductory Notes (Box 21)
  - Preface, Table of Contents (Box 21)
  - Sources to be found for Core I (Box 21)
  - Core/Elemental words (Box 21)
  - Core words: unclassified (Box 21)
  - Corrections and additions for Core words (Box 21)
  - Useless panel (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous article (Box 21)
  - Diana Davis (Box 21)
  - Notes from Diana (Box 21)
  - J & M (Box 21)
  - Rules for typist (Box 21)
  - Websters' "Intergalactic Seal of Approval" and "Intergalactic Wickedary" (Box 22)
  - Websters' "Intergalactic Seal of Approval" and "Intergalactic Wickedary" (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Contents (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Preface (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Explanatory Notes and Cover (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Word Web I (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Web One - The Wickedary: Its History/Metamystery (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Word Web II (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Web Two - Spelling: The Casting of Spells (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Web Three - Grammar: Our Wicked Witches' Hammer (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Web Four - Pronunciation: Denouncing, Pronouncing, Announcing (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Web Five - Guides to the Wickedary (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Appendicular Webs (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Appendicular Web One (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Appendicular Web Two - Be-Laughing (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Appendicular Web Three - Spinning (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Appendicular Web Four - Jumping (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Endnotes and notes (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Illustrations and captions (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Core I (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Core II (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Core III (Box 22)
  - Wickedary Core III and Dummies, clippings, shuttle explosion (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix I, part 1 - Dummies of the First Class (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix I, part 2 - Dummies of the Second Class (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix I, part 3 - Antibiotics wn Elementaries, Third Class (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix I, part 5 - Reversals (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix I, part 6 - Pseudo-Feminist Dummies (Box 22)
  - Clippings for Appendix II - The Cardinals New Clothes (Box 22)
  - Appendix III - Sense of Direction (Box 22)
  - Appendix IV - Off the Clock, Chernobyl (Box 22)
  - Loose in Box, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
  - Periodicals, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Notes (Box 22)
  - The Be-Dazzling Voyage: Spiraling into the Nineties (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Notes (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust General Outline (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Chapter One: Lust/Lusty - volcanoes, animal abuse (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Two: Pope - sublime, divine, attributes, omnipotence/omniscience/omnipresence (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Three: Sublimation - doctrine of incarnation, plastic women, pro-life, sacrifice and suffering, torture (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Four: Sublimation - charity, therapy (Box 22)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Four: Sublimation - born agains, Pope, doublethink/doubletalk, nuclear missions (nuclearism, Three Mile Island, Trident, build-up), plastic humor, plastic passions, preaching, sacraments (baptism, confirmation, extreme unction, holy orders, matrimony), 1980 (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Four: Sublimation - subliminals, theatre, third world, Islam and Third World War, mediated experience and knowledge, missionaries/priests (bonding, Reagan, secrecy), missions (nuclear) (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Five: Touchable Caste/Race - animals, elements (air, earth, water) (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Five: Touchable Caste/Race - female masochism, chemical and nuclear waste, women waste (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Six: Breaking Out - volcanoes (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Seven: Tides/Tidy - Athenas, demons, tides, time, therapy, animals, chemical contaminators and agents (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Seven: Tides/Tidy - future, gadget, hospitals, lesbophobia, media, nuclear weapons and energy, venting, obsession (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Seven: Tides/Tidy - plastic surgery, prosthesis, police as agents, pseudo-feminism, space, speed, time, women's lifetime (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Eight: Auras, Atmosphere, Angels (Box 23)
  - Pure Lust Chapter Nine: Wanderlust (Box 23)
  - Spheres, 1980 (Box 23)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Sudie Rakusin - Cow jumping over the moon, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Terrie Reidwein (Box 23)
  - Roseanne (Box 23)
  - Notes (Box 23)
  - New Yorker article, 1996 (Box 23)
  - Quintessence contract, 1996 (Box 23)
  - Manuscript pages - Third Word Web (Box 23)
  - The Church and the Second Sex New Archaic Afterwards (Box 23)
  - Promotional Tour, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Pages from book (Wickedary?) (Box 23)
  - Various manuscript pages (Box 23)
  - Outercourse drafts (Box 23)
  - Wickedary proposal (Box 23)
  - Quintessence promo (Box 23)
  - Beyond God the Father reviews (Box 23)
  - Church and the Second Sex - submitted to BC re. professorship (Box 23)
  - Outercourse contract, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Excerpts from The Church and the Second Sex in Japanese (Box 24)
  - Crone-ology, 1979 (Box 24)
  - New York Times Book Reviews of Mary Daly's Five Books, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Outercourse contract, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Wickedary photos (Box 24)
  - Alaska Women's Bookstore (Box 24)
  - Wickedary proposal (Box 24)
  - Montreal Massacre, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Outercourse Introduction (Box 24)
  - Outercourse Prelude (Box 24)
  - Outercourse Chapters 1-20 (Box 24)
  - Mary Daly notes on books pp. 1-112 (Box 24)
  - Great Wind notes (Box 24)
  - Wickedary World Web One (Box 24)
  - Wickedary Cores I - III (Box 24)
  - Outercourse draft (Box 24)
  - Pure Lust marketing (Box 24)
  - Outercourse Index (Box 24)
  - Barbara Flanagan, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Corrections for Galaxy (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Outercourse notes (Box 24)
  - Outercourse New Introduction to Chapter 15 (Box 25)
  - Outercourse Galleys (Box 25)
  - Index of New Words (Box 25)
  - Outercourse Galley Proofs 1 - 2 (Box 25)
  - Outercourse Index and Chapter Notes (Box 25)
  - Facsimile corrections, 1992 (Box 26)
  - Barbara's copies (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1992 (Box 26)
  - Outercourse Preface (Box 26)
  - Prelude to Third Spiral Galaxy (Box 26)
  - Outercourse Chapters 8, 11 - 20 (Box 26)
  - Beyond God the Father original manuscript (Box 26)
  - Beyond God the Father Introduction, Notes and Chapters 1 - 7 (Box 26)
  - Beyond God the Father Proof (Box 26)
  - Beyond God the Father Galley proof (Box 26)
  - Beyond God the Father Second Proof (Box 26)
  - The Turned-on Generation and the Church (aborted) (Box 27)
  - The Church and the Second Sex Research II (Box 27)
  - Outercourse Galley Proofs 1 - 2, Chapters 1-20, conclusion and notes (Box 27)
  - The Church and the Second Sex book reviews (Box 27)
  - Beyond God the Father British reviews, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Wickedary reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 27)
  - Pure Lust book reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 27)
  - Pure Lust reviews, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
  - General articles, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
  - The Church and the Second Sex research introduction, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
  - The Church and the Second Sex manuscript (Box 27)
  - Catholocism: Death or Rebirth? unpublished manuscript (Box 27)
  - Manuscripts of speeches, partial collection, 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - The Church and the Second Sex Research II, 1964-1970 (Box 27)
  - Beyond God the Father French manuscript (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father French index drafts (Box 28)
  - Dictionary of the history of Ideas galleys and manuscripts (Box 28)
  - Catholicism: Death or Rebirth unpublished, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father corrections (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father pre-printing, 1973 (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father French translation (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father German translation (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father Index (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father French edition, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father Page Proofs (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father unrevised incomplete manuscript (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father manuscript, early form (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father almost final manuscript (Box 28)
  - Gyn/Ecology? (Box 28)
  - Beyond God the Father royalties, 1994 (Box 28)
  - Current biography (Claggett), 1996 (Box 28)
  - Gyn/Ecology - Beacon Press, 1994 (Box 28)
  - Agents - Frances Goldin literary agent, etc., 1994 (Box 28)
  - G.E.D. and Wickedary (Box 28)
  - Author's royalty, 1998 (Box 28)
  - Church and the Second Sex II: Feminist PostChristian Introduction (Box 28)
  - Harper foreign translation, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Church and the Second Sex II Feminist PostChristian Introduction (Box 29)
  - Boston College Underground Church - conferences organized (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex - Chapman, contracts, 1965-1971 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous material on Collins and Macmillan - Chapman, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex - Chapman - legal matters, foreign editors, release of rights, royalties, correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex - Harper and Row - legal correspondence, promotional material, 1966-1971 (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex - correspondence, publicity, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex II correspondence, PostChristian intro., Harper Colophon publicity, 1974-1976 (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex II repros (Box 29)
  - Beyond, Gyn/Ecology foreign rights, German, 1974-1989 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology P.R., blurbs, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology - Beacon, speaking, p.r., 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Beacon Press: publicity, receipts, 1972-1984 (Box 29)
  - Charlotte Raymond (Box 29)
  - Beyond God the Father - Ruether - Christianity and Crisis (Box 29)
  - Beacon - Gobin, Stair (Director), women (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology - correspondence, reviews, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology - adoptions (Box 29)
  - Beacon Press - Gyn/Ecology corrections (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology Emily's sketches (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology illustrations (Box 29)
  - Beacon - Gyn/Ecology foreign rights, Virago, Pat Harrison, 1973-1981 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology Elaine Markson and other agents, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology interviews, Sojourner, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology - paperback, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Gyn/Ecology permissions fees and Beyond God the Father, 1979-1982 (Box 29)
  - Mary Daly articles (Box 29)
  - Scott Ellis, 2007 (Box 29)
  - Spiralina into the 1990's and other Daly articles, 2003 (Box 29)
  - Loose paper in box, 2006 (Box 29)
  - What is Wrong with "God"? Everything. Mary Daly article (Box 29)
  - Church and the Second Sex Japanese versions (Box 29)
  - Wickedary - submitted for full professorship, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Pure Lust - submitted for full professorship, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Amazon Grace sources, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Beyond God the Father reviews for EEOC, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - Amazon Grace (Box 29)
  - Outercourse flyers regarding speaking engagements, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Outercourse ada and catalogues (Box 29)
  - Outercourse, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Clayton Caileon, 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse, 1991-1993 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Permissions, 1990-1993 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Hard Cover, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Harper Catalog, 1994 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Press Release (Box 30)
  - Harper Royalties, 1993-1996 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary Harper Royalties, 1993-1995 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Harper Royalties, 1993-1995 (Box 30)
  - Harper's Promotional Matierial, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Beyond God the Father Beacon Permissions, 1994-1998 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary Permissions, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Frauenoffensive Contracts, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Harper Paperback, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Frauenoffensive Publicity, 1995 (Box 30)
  - Frauenoffensive Royalties, 1983-1995 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary Harper, 1988-1993 (Box 30)
  - Qualitative Leap St Martin's Press, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Spinifex Contract, 1992-1995 (Box 30)
  - Spinifex Royalties, 1994-1998 (Box 30)
  - Spinifex Reviews, 1993-1997 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary Publicity Women's Press, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Women's Press Catalog, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Women's Press Kathy Gale, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Women's Press Royalties, 1979-1996 (Box 30)
  - Outercourse British Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary British Reviews (Box 30)
  - Outercourse Women's Press Excerpts, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Wickedary Women's Press Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 30)
  - Pure Lust Women's Press, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Beyond God the Father Women's Press Reviews, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Gyn/Ecology Women's Press, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Radio Pacifica Contract, 1989-1993 (Box 30)
  - KPFK, 1988-1993 (Box 30)